[{"subjectID":"80vf3pb1k1","prolificID":"63d2094a50ed63bfb3b19fd4","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215604845e735e066f1e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664163747,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":0,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"146","question":"Describe the last time you went to the zoo.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":22,"rt":21734,"timeElapsed":89801},{"subjectID":"80vf3pb1k1","prolificID":"63d2094a50ed63bfb3b19fd4","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215604845e735e066f1e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664187371,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":1,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"146","question":"Describe the last time you went to the zoo.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":10,"rt":23623,"timeElapsed":113424},{"subjectID":"80vf3pb1k1","prolificID":"63d2094a50ed63bfb3b19fd4","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215604845e735e066f1e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664209067,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":2,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"146","question":"Describe the last time you went to the zoo.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":8,"rt":21695,"timeElapsed":135121},{"subjectID":"80vf3pb1k1","prolificID":"63d2094a50ed63bfb3b19fd4","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215604845e735e066f1e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664226762,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":3,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"146","question":"Describe the last time you went to the zoo.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":7,"rt":17695,"timeElapsed":152816},{"subjectID":"80vf3pb1k1","prolificID":"63d2094a50ed63bfb3b19fd4","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215604845e735e066f1e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664237682,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":4,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"146","question":"Describe the last time you went to the zoo.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":17,"rt":10919,"timeElapsed":163736},{"subjectID":"80vf3pb1k1","prolificID":"63d2094a50ed63bfb3b19fd4","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215604845e735e066f1e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664246939,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":5,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"146","question":"Describe the last time you went to the zoo.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":4,"rt":9255,"timeElapsed":172993},{"subjectID":"80vf3pb1k1","prolificID":"63d2094a50ed63bfb3b19fd4","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215604845e735e066f1e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664251810,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":6,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"146","question":"Describe the last time you went to the zoo.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":2,"rt":4871,"timeElapsed":177864},{"subjectID":"80vf3pb1k1","prolificID":"63d2094a50ed63bfb3b19fd4","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215604845e735e066f1e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664267410,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":7,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"146","question":"Describe the last time you went to the zoo.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":9,"rt":15599,"timeElapsed":193464},{"subjectID":"80vf3pb1k1","prolificID":"63d2094a50ed63bfb3b19fd4","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215604845e735e066f1e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664286434,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":8,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"146","question":"Describe the last time you went to the zoo.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":15,"rt":19023,"timeElapsed":212488},{"subjectID":"80vf3pb1k1","prolificID":"63d2094a50ed63bfb3b19fd4","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215604845e735e066f1e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664308202,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":9,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"213","question":"Do you enjoy staying in hotels? What do you like or not like about them?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":37,"rt":19279,"timeElapsed":234256},{"subjectID":"80vf3pb1k1","prolificID":"63d2094a50ed63bfb3b19fd4","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215604845e735e066f1e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664318955,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":10,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"213","question":"Do you enjoy staying in hotels? What do you like or not like about them?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":28,"rt":10752,"timeElapsed":245009},{"subjectID":"80vf3pb1k1","prolificID":"63d2094a50ed63bfb3b19fd4","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215604845e735e066f1e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664329410,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":11,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"213","question":"Do you enjoy staying in hotels? What do you like or not like about them?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":46,"rt":10455,"timeElapsed":255464},{"subjectID":"80vf3pb1k1","prolificID":"63d2094a50ed63bfb3b19fd4","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215604845e735e066f1e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664335450,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":12,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"213","question":"Do you enjoy staying in hotels? What do you like or not like about them?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":29,"rt":6039,"timeElapsed":261504},{"subjectID":"80vf3pb1k1","prolificID":"63d2094a50ed63bfb3b19fd4","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215604845e735e066f1e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664344322,"comprehensionCheck":1,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":0,"trialIdx":12,"questionIdx":null,"scaleIdx":null,"questionID":null,"question":"Do you enjoy staying in hotels? What do you like or not like about them?","questionCategory":"comprehension check","scaleID":null,"scaleBlock":null,"scaleText":"Please drag the slider all the way to the end labeled STRAWBERRY","scaleTextMin":"STRAWBERRY","scaleTextMax":"PINEAPPLE","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":8871,"timeElapsed":270376},{"subjectID":"80vf3pb1k1","prolificID":"63d2094a50ed63bfb3b19fd4","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215604845e735e066f1e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664353866,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":13,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"213","question":"Do you enjoy staying in hotels? What do you like or not like about them?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":55,"rt":9543,"timeElapsed":279920},{"subjectID":"80vf3pb1k1","prolificID":"63d2094a50ed63bfb3b19fd4","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215604845e735e066f1e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664360266,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":14,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"213","question":"Do you enjoy staying in hotels? What do you like or not like about them?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":20,"rt":6399,"timeElapsed":286320},{"subjectID":"80vf3pb1k1","prolificID":"63d2094a50ed63bfb3b19fd4","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215604845e735e066f1e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664366746,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":15,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"213","question":"Do you enjoy staying in hotels? What do you like or not like about them?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":16,"rt":6479,"timeElapsed":292800},{"subjectID":"80vf3pb1k1","prolificID":"63d2094a50ed63bfb3b19fd4","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215604845e735e066f1e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664384035,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":16,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"213","question":"Do you enjoy staying in hotels? What do you like or not like about them?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":11,"rt":17288,"timeElapsed":310089},{"subjectID":"80vf3pb1k1","prolificID":"63d2094a50ed63bfb3b19fd4","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215604845e735e066f1e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664391906,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":17,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"213","question":"Do you enjoy staying in hotels? What do you like or not like about them?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":19,"rt":7871,"timeElapsed":317960},{"subjectID":"80vf3pb1k1","prolificID":"63d2094a50ed63bfb3b19fd4","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215604845e735e066f1e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664424290,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":18,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"247","question":"Do you think of yourself as \"handy\" when it comes to building things or doing home improvement? If so, describe a time you recently used this skill. If not, describe what you do when you need something fixed.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":44,"rt":30711,"timeElapsed":350344},{"subjectID":"80vf3pb1k1","prolificID":"63d2094a50ed63bfb3b19fd4","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215604845e735e066f1e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664430498,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":19,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"247","question":"Do you think of yourself as \"handy\" when it comes to building things or doing home improvement? If so, describe a time you recently used this skill. If not, describe what you do when you need something fixed.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":53,"rt":6207,"timeElapsed":356552},{"subjectID":"80vf3pb1k1","prolificID":"63d2094a50ed63bfb3b19fd4","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215604845e735e066f1e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664436570,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":20,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"247","question":"Do you think of yourself as \"handy\" when it comes to building things or doing home improvement? If so, describe a time you recently used this skill. If not, describe what you do when you need something fixed.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":40,"rt":6071,"timeElapsed":362624},{"subjectID":"80vf3pb1k1","prolificID":"63d2094a50ed63bfb3b19fd4","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215604845e735e066f1e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664441587,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":21,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"247","question":"Do you think of yourself as \"handy\" when it comes to building things or doing home improvement? If so, describe a time you recently used this skill. If not, describe what you do when you need something fixed.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":51,"rt":5016,"timeElapsed":367641},{"subjectID":"80vf3pb1k1","prolificID":"63d2094a50ed63bfb3b19fd4","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215604845e735e066f1e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664447650,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":22,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"247","question":"Do you think of yourself as \"handy\" when it comes to building things or doing home improvement? If so, describe a time you recently used this skill. If not, describe what you do when you need something fixed.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":57,"rt":6063,"timeElapsed":373704},{"subjectID":"80vf3pb1k1","prolificID":"63d2094a50ed63bfb3b19fd4","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215604845e735e066f1e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664452258,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":23,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"247","question":"Do you think of yourself as \"handy\" when it comes to building things or doing home improvement? If so, describe a time you recently used this skill. If not, describe what you do when you need something fixed.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":21,"rt":4608,"timeElapsed":378312},{"subjectID":"80vf3pb1k1","prolificID":"63d2094a50ed63bfb3b19fd4","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215604845e735e066f1e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664456890,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":24,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"247","question":"Do you think of yourself as \"handy\" when it comes to building things or doing home improvement? If so, describe a time you recently used this skill. If not, describe what you do when you need something fixed.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":12,"rt":4632,"timeElapsed":382944},{"subjectID":"80vf3pb1k1","prolificID":"63d2094a50ed63bfb3b19fd4","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215604845e735e066f1e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664464282,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":25,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"247","question":"Do you think of yourself as \"handy\" when it comes to building things or doing home improvement? If so, describe a time you recently used this skill. If not, describe what you do when you need something fixed.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":15,"rt":7391,"timeElapsed":390336},{"subjectID":"80vf3pb1k1","prolificID":"63d2094a50ed63bfb3b19fd4","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215604845e735e066f1e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664470330,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":26,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"247","question":"Do you think of yourself as \"handy\" when it comes to building things or doing home improvement? If so, describe a time you recently used this skill. If not, describe what you do when you need something fixed.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":11,"rt":6048,"timeElapsed":396384},{"subjectID":"80vf3pb1k1","prolificID":"63d2094a50ed63bfb3b19fd4","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215604845e735e066f1e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664486474,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":27,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"87","question":"If you could see or listen to one work of art as you die, what would it be?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":9,"rt":14536,"timeElapsed":412528},{"subjectID":"80vf3pb1k1","prolificID":"63d2094a50ed63bfb3b19fd4","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215604845e735e066f1e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664490714,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":28,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"87","question":"If you could see or listen to one work of art as you die, what would it be?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":13,"rt":4239,"timeElapsed":416768},{"subjectID":"80vf3pb1k1","prolificID":"63d2094a50ed63bfb3b19fd4","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215604845e735e066f1e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664499226,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":29,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"87","question":"If you could see or listen to one work of art as you die, what would it be?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":27,"rt":8511,"timeElapsed":425280},{"subjectID":"80vf3pb1k1","prolificID":"63d2094a50ed63bfb3b19fd4","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215604845e735e066f1e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664503659,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":30,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"87","question":"If you could see or listen to one work of art as you die, what would it be?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":20,"rt":4432,"timeElapsed":429713},{"subjectID":"80vf3pb1k1","prolificID":"63d2094a50ed63bfb3b19fd4","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215604845e735e066f1e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664509162,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":31,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"87","question":"If you could see or listen to one work of art as you die, what would it be?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":7,"rt":5503,"timeElapsed":435216},{"subjectID":"80vf3pb1k1","prolificID":"63d2094a50ed63bfb3b19fd4","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215604845e735e066f1e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664513138,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":32,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"87","question":"If you could see or listen to one work of art as you die, what would it be?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":58,"rt":3975,"timeElapsed":439192},{"subjectID":"80vf3pb1k1","prolificID":"63d2094a50ed63bfb3b19fd4","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215604845e735e066f1e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664518347,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":33,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"87","question":"If you could see or listen to one work of art as you die, what would it be?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":57,"rt":5208,"timeElapsed":444401},{"subjectID":"80vf3pb1k1","prolificID":"63d2094a50ed63bfb3b19fd4","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215604845e735e066f1e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664533386,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":34,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"87","question":"If you could see or listen to one work of art as you die, what would it be?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":32,"rt":15039,"timeElapsed":459440},{"subjectID":"80vf3pb1k1","prolificID":"63d2094a50ed63bfb3b19fd4","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215604845e735e066f1e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664540386,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":35,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"87","question":"If you could see or listen to one work of art as you die, what would it be?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":40,"rt":6999,"timeElapsed":466440},{"subjectID":"80vf3pb1k1","prolificID":"63d2094a50ed63bfb3b19fd4","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215604845e735e066f1e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664564363,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":36,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"154","question":"Who is your favorite actor or actress? Describe a favorite scene in which this person has acted.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":30,"rt":21984,"timeElapsed":490417},{"subjectID":"80vf3pb1k1","prolificID":"63d2094a50ed63bfb3b19fd4","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215604845e735e066f1e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664568458,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":37,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"154","question":"Who is your favorite actor or actress? Describe a favorite scene in which this person has acted.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":22,"rt":4095,"timeElapsed":494512},{"subjectID":"80vf3pb1k1","prolificID":"63d2094a50ed63bfb3b19fd4","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215604845e735e066f1e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664574730,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":38,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"154","question":"Who is your favorite actor or actress? Describe a favorite scene in which this person has acted.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":41,"rt":6272,"timeElapsed":500784},{"subjectID":"80vf3pb1k1","prolificID":"63d2094a50ed63bfb3b19fd4","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215604845e735e066f1e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664578146,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":39,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"154","question":"Who is your favorite actor or actress? Describe a favorite scene in which this person has acted.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":29,"rt":3415,"timeElapsed":504200},{"subjectID":"80vf3pb1k1","prolificID":"63d2094a50ed63bfb3b19fd4","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215604845e735e066f1e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664588378,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":40,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"154","question":"Who is your favorite actor or actress? Describe a favorite scene in which this person has acted.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":21,"rt":10232,"timeElapsed":514432},{"subjectID":"80vf3pb1k1","prolificID":"63d2094a50ed63bfb3b19fd4","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215604845e735e066f1e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664592562,"comprehensionCheck":1,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":100,"trialIdx":40,"questionIdx":null,"scaleIdx":null,"questionID":null,"question":"Who is your favorite actor or actress? Describe a favorite scene in which this person has acted.","questionCategory":"comprehension check","scaleID":null,"scaleBlock":null,"scaleText":"Please drag the slider all the way to the end labeled HAMBURGER","scaleTextMin":"HOTDOG","scaleTextMax":"HAMBURGER","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":4183,"timeElapsed":518616},{"subjectID":"80vf3pb1k1","prolificID":"63d2094a50ed63bfb3b19fd4","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215604845e735e066f1e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664598835,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":41,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"154","question":"Who is your favorite actor or actress? Describe a favorite scene in which this person has acted.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":15,"rt":6272,"timeElapsed":524888},{"subjectID":"80vf3pb1k1","prolificID":"63d2094a50ed63bfb3b19fd4","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215604845e735e066f1e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664602882,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":42,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"154","question":"Who is your favorite actor or actress? Describe a favorite scene in which this person has acted.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":9,"rt":4047,"timeElapsed":528936},{"subjectID":"80vf3pb1k1","prolificID":"63d2094a50ed63bfb3b19fd4","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215604845e735e066f1e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664611426,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":43,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"154","question":"Who is your favorite actor or actress? Describe a favorite scene in which this person has acted.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":12,"rt":8543,"timeElapsed":537480},{"subjectID":"80vf3pb1k1","prolificID":"63d2094a50ed63bfb3b19fd4","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215604845e735e066f1e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664618306,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":44,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"154","question":"Who is your favorite actor or actress? Describe a favorite scene in which this person has acted.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":7,"rt":6879,"timeElapsed":544360},{"subjectID":"80vf3pb1k1","prolificID":"63d2094a50ed63bfb3b19fd4","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215604845e735e066f1e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664634338,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":45,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"45","question":"Do you think of yourself as introverted or extraverted? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":64,"rt":14215,"timeElapsed":560392},{"subjectID":"80vf3pb1k1","prolificID":"63d2094a50ed63bfb3b19fd4","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215604845e735e066f1e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664639938,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":46,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"45","question":"Do you think of yourself as introverted or extraverted? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":56,"rt":5600,"timeElapsed":565992},{"subjectID":"80vf3pb1k1","prolificID":"63d2094a50ed63bfb3b19fd4","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215604845e735e066f1e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664649298,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":47,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"45","question":"Do you think of yourself as introverted or extraverted? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":67,"rt":9359,"timeElapsed":575352},{"subjectID":"80vf3pb1k1","prolificID":"63d2094a50ed63bfb3b19fd4","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215604845e735e066f1e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664655018,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":48,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"45","question":"Do you think of yourself as introverted or extraverted? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":53,"rt":5719,"timeElapsed":581072},{"subjectID":"80vf3pb1k1","prolificID":"63d2094a50ed63bfb3b19fd4","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215604845e735e066f1e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664666274,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":49,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"45","question":"Do you think of yourself as introverted or extraverted? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":60,"rt":11255,"timeElapsed":592328},{"subjectID":"80vf3pb1k1","prolificID":"63d2094a50ed63bfb3b19fd4","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215604845e735e066f1e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664670667,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":50,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"45","question":"Do you think of yourself as introverted or extraverted? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":71,"rt":4392,"timeElapsed":596721},{"subjectID":"80vf3pb1k1","prolificID":"63d2094a50ed63bfb3b19fd4","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215604845e735e066f1e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664677058,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":51,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"45","question":"Do you think of yourself as introverted or extraverted? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":60,"rt":6391,"timeElapsed":603112},{"subjectID":"80vf3pb1k1","prolificID":"63d2094a50ed63bfb3b19fd4","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215604845e735e066f1e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664686914,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":52,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"45","question":"Do you think of yourself as introverted or extraverted? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":26,"rt":9855,"timeElapsed":612968},{"subjectID":"80vf3pb1k1","prolificID":"63d2094a50ed63bfb3b19fd4","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215604845e735e066f1e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664692474,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":53,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"45","question":"Do you think of yourself as introverted or extraverted? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":19,"rt":5560,"timeElapsed":618528},{"subjectID":"80vf3pb1k1","prolificID":"63d2094a50ed63bfb3b19fd4","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215604845e735e066f1e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664705450,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":54,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"122","question":"What do you wish your parents did differently in raising you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":69,"rt":11639,"timeElapsed":631504},{"subjectID":"80vf3pb1k1","prolificID":"63d2094a50ed63bfb3b19fd4","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215604845e735e066f1e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664712970,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":55,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"122","question":"What do you wish your parents did differently in raising you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":63,"rt":7519,"timeElapsed":639024},{"subjectID":"80vf3pb1k1","prolificID":"63d2094a50ed63bfb3b19fd4","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215604845e735e066f1e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664725666,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":56,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"122","question":"What do you wish your parents did differently in raising you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":66,"rt":12695,"timeElapsed":651720},{"subjectID":"80vf3pb1k1","prolificID":"63d2094a50ed63bfb3b19fd4","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215604845e735e066f1e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664734035,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":57,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"122","question":"What do you wish your parents did differently in raising you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":62,"rt":8368,"timeElapsed":660089},{"subjectID":"80vf3pb1k1","prolificID":"63d2094a50ed63bfb3b19fd4","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215604845e735e066f1e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664742522,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":58,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"122","question":"What do you wish your parents did differently in raising you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":54,"rt":8487,"timeElapsed":668576},{"subjectID":"80vf3pb1k1","prolificID":"63d2094a50ed63bfb3b19fd4","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215604845e735e066f1e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664746547,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":59,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"122","question":"What do you wish your parents did differently in raising you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":87,"rt":4024,"timeElapsed":672601},{"subjectID":"80vf3pb1k1","prolificID":"63d2094a50ed63bfb3b19fd4","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215604845e735e066f1e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664753746,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":60,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"122","question":"What do you wish your parents did differently in raising you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":86,"rt":7199,"timeElapsed":679800},{"subjectID":"80vf3pb1k1","prolificID":"63d2094a50ed63bfb3b19fd4","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215604845e735e066f1e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664762330,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":61,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"122","question":"What do you wish your parents did differently in raising you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":66,"rt":8583,"timeElapsed":688384},{"subjectID":"80vf3pb1k1","prolificID":"63d2094a50ed63bfb3b19fd4","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215604845e735e066f1e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664767786,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":62,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"122","question":"What do you wish your parents did differently in raising you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":71,"rt":5455,"timeElapsed":693840},{"subjectID":"80vf3pb1k1","prolificID":"63d2094a50ed63bfb3b19fd4","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215604845e735e066f1e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664791282,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":63,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"31","question":"Your current home, containing everything you own, catches fire. After saving your loved ones and pets, you have time to safely make a final dash to save any one item. What would it be? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":24,"rt":21831,"timeElapsed":717336},{"subjectID":"80vf3pb1k1","prolificID":"63d2094a50ed63bfb3b19fd4","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215604845e735e066f1e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664795539,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":64,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"31","question":"Your current home, containing everything you own, catches fire. After saving your loved ones and pets, you have time to safely make a final dash to save any one item. What would it be? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":13,"rt":4256,"timeElapsed":721593},{"subjectID":"80vf3pb1k1","prolificID":"63d2094a50ed63bfb3b19fd4","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215604845e735e066f1e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664800634,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":65,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"31","question":"Your current home, containing everything you own, catches fire. After saving your loved ones and pets, you have time to safely make a final dash to save any one item. What would it be? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":20,"rt":5095,"timeElapsed":726688},{"subjectID":"80vf3pb1k1","prolificID":"63d2094a50ed63bfb3b19fd4","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215604845e735e066f1e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664804378,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":66,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"31","question":"Your current home, containing everything you own, catches fire. After saving your loved ones and pets, you have time to safely make a final dash to save any one item. What would it be? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":11,"rt":3743,"timeElapsed":730432},{"subjectID":"80vf3pb1k1","prolificID":"63d2094a50ed63bfb3b19fd4","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215604845e735e066f1e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664809562,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":67,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"31","question":"Your current home, containing everything you own, catches fire. After saving your loved ones and pets, you have time to safely make a final dash to save any one item. What would it be? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":14,"rt":5183,"timeElapsed":735616},{"subjectID":"80vf3pb1k1","prolificID":"63d2094a50ed63bfb3b19fd4","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215604845e735e066f1e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664813890,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":68,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"31","question":"Your current home, containing everything you own, catches fire. After saving your loved ones and pets, you have time to safely make a final dash to save any one item. What would it be? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":8,"rt":4327,"timeElapsed":739944},{"subjectID":"80vf3pb1k1","prolificID":"63d2094a50ed63bfb3b19fd4","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215604845e735e066f1e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664817874,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":69,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"31","question":"Your current home, containing everything you own, catches fire. After saving your loved ones and pets, you have time to safely make a final dash to save any one item. What would it be? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":8,"rt":3984,"timeElapsed":743928},{"subjectID":"80vf3pb1k1","prolificID":"63d2094a50ed63bfb3b19fd4","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215604845e735e066f1e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664823898,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":70,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"31","question":"Your current home, containing everything you own, catches fire. After saving your loved ones and pets, you have time to safely make a final dash to save any one item. What would it be? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":11,"rt":6023,"timeElapsed":749952},{"subjectID":"80vf3pb1k1","prolificID":"63d2094a50ed63bfb3b19fd4","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215604845e735e066f1e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664828122,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":71,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"31","question":"Your current home, containing everything you own, catches fire. After saving your loved ones and pets, you have time to safely make a final dash to save any one item. What would it be? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":17,"rt":4223,"timeElapsed":754176},{"subjectID":"80vf3pb1k1","prolificID":"63d2094a50ed63bfb3b19fd4","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215604845e735e066f1e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664847642,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":72,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"233","question":"If you could telepathically control one crocodile, what would you do with this ability?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":22,"rt":17991,"timeElapsed":773696},{"subjectID":"80vf3pb1k1","prolificID":"63d2094a50ed63bfb3b19fd4","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215604845e735e066f1e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664851323,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":73,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"233","question":"If you could telepathically control one crocodile, what would you do with this ability?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":14,"rt":3680,"timeElapsed":777377},{"subjectID":"80vf3pb1k1","prolificID":"63d2094a50ed63bfb3b19fd4","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215604845e735e066f1e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664854890,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":74,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"233","question":"If you could telepathically control one crocodile, what would you do with this ability?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":22,"rt":3566,"timeElapsed":780944},{"subjectID":"80vf3pb1k1","prolificID":"63d2094a50ed63bfb3b19fd4","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215604845e735e066f1e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664858594,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":75,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"233","question":"If you could telepathically control one crocodile, what would you do with this ability?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":9,"rt":3703,"timeElapsed":784648},{"subjectID":"80vf3pb1k1","prolificID":"63d2094a50ed63bfb3b19fd4","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215604845e735e066f1e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664863186,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":76,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"233","question":"If you could telepathically control one crocodile, what would you do with this ability?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":6,"rt":4592,"timeElapsed":789240},{"subjectID":"80vf3pb1k1","prolificID":"63d2094a50ed63bfb3b19fd4","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215604845e735e066f1e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664868202,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":77,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"233","question":"If you could telepathically control one crocodile, what would you do with this ability?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":19,"rt":5016,"timeElapsed":794256},{"subjectID":"80vf3pb1k1","prolificID":"63d2094a50ed63bfb3b19fd4","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215604845e735e066f1e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664872802,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":78,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"233","question":"If you could telepathically control one crocodile, what would you do with this ability?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":7,"rt":4599,"timeElapsed":798856},{"subjectID":"80vf3pb1k1","prolificID":"63d2094a50ed63bfb3b19fd4","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215604845e735e066f1e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664877082,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":79,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"233","question":"If you could telepathically control one crocodile, what would you do with this ability?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":21,"rt":4280,"timeElapsed":803136},{"subjectID":"80vf3pb1k1","prolificID":"63d2094a50ed63bfb3b19fd4","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215604845e735e066f1e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664880619,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":80,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"233","question":"If you could telepathically control one crocodile, what would you do with this ability?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":23,"rt":3536,"timeElapsed":806673},{"subjectID":"80vf3pb1k1","prolificID":"63d2094a50ed63bfb3b19fd4","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215604845e735e066f1e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664895610,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":81,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"57","question":"Do you think your children (or the next generation of children) will inherit a world that is overall better than the current one or worse? In what ways will the future be better or worse?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":76,"rt":13400,"timeElapsed":821664},{"subjectID":"80vf3pb1k1","prolificID":"63d2094a50ed63bfb3b19fd4","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215604845e735e066f1e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664899938,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":82,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"57","question":"Do you think your children (or the next generation of children) will inherit a world that is overall better than the current one or worse? In what ways will the future be better or worse?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":81,"rt":4327,"timeElapsed":825992},{"subjectID":"80vf3pb1k1","prolificID":"63d2094a50ed63bfb3b19fd4","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215604845e735e066f1e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664906314,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":83,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"57","question":"Do you think your children (or the next generation of children) will inherit a world that is overall better than the current one or worse? In what ways will the future be better or worse?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":84,"rt":6375,"timeElapsed":832368},{"subjectID":"80vf3pb1k1","prolificID":"63d2094a50ed63bfb3b19fd4","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215604845e735e066f1e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664910834,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":84,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"57","question":"Do you think your children (or the next generation of children) will inherit a world that is overall better than the current one or worse? In what ways will the future be better or worse?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":73,"rt":4519,"timeElapsed":836888},{"subjectID":"80vf3pb1k1","prolificID":"63d2094a50ed63bfb3b19fd4","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215604845e735e066f1e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664915418,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":85,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"57","question":"Do you think your children (or the next generation of children) will inherit a world that is overall better than the current one or worse? In what ways will the future be better or worse?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":74,"rt":4583,"timeElapsed":841472},{"subjectID":"80vf3pb1k1","prolificID":"63d2094a50ed63bfb3b19fd4","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215604845e735e066f1e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664920002,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":86,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"57","question":"Do you think your children (or the next generation of children) will inherit a world that is overall better than the current one or worse? In what ways will the future be better or worse?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":76,"rt":4584,"timeElapsed":846056},{"subjectID":"80vf3pb1k1","prolificID":"63d2094a50ed63bfb3b19fd4","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215604845e735e066f1e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664927986,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":87,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"57","question":"Do you think your children (or the next generation of children) will inherit a world that is overall better than the current one or worse? In what ways will the future be better or worse?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":81,"rt":7983,"timeElapsed":854040},{"subjectID":"80vf3pb1k1","prolificID":"63d2094a50ed63bfb3b19fd4","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215604845e735e066f1e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664938346,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":88,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"57","question":"Do you think your children (or the next generation of children) will inherit a world that is overall better than the current one or worse? In what ways will the future be better or worse?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":50,"rt":10359,"timeElapsed":864400},{"subjectID":"80vf3pb1k1","prolificID":"63d2094a50ed63bfb3b19fd4","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774215604845e735e066f1e","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664947258,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":89,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"57","question":"Do you think your children (or the next generation of children) will inherit a world that is overall better than the current one or worse? In what ways will the future be better or worse?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":56,"rt":8912,"timeElapsed":873312}]